walk to sink
put plate
put plate on the side
pick filter
open
put water into the coffee machine
close coffee machine
press button
put water filter down
open cupboard
pick mug
close cupboard
put cup
pick plate
close cupboard
put plate down
pick cereal
remove bag from cereal
open bag
put cereal in plate
put cereal box away
close bag
return bag into cereal box
put cereal box away
press button
open fridge
pick up milk
close fridge
put milk into cup
put milk into plate
close milk
open fridge
return milk
close fridge
open drawer
pick up two spoons
put spoon into the cereal plate
press button
open sugar jar
scoop sugar
put sugar into the coffee
close sugar jar
stir sugar
stir the coffee in the mug
pick up mug
mistake did not change the coffee pot
empty water
open sink
close sink
sink mug
put cup
pick up coffee pot
open the coffee machine
put coffee pot
close coffee machine
put mug
press button
open fridge
pick up milk
close fridge
put milk in cup
close milk
open milk
put milk
close fridge
hold sugar jar
open sugar jar
scoop sugar
put sugar
stir coffee mug
close sugar jar
wait for coffee
pick up water filter
open coffee machine
fill water into the coffee machine and close the lid
put water filter
press button
wait for coffee
stir coffee
keep stirring coffee
pick up spoon
put spoon in sink
hold mug
keep holding mug
press button
pick up mug
[END SUBTITLE]